makelovenotporn.com 2016-11-19

# Make Love Not Porn :: Porn World vs. Real World

  * Home
  * About
  * Buy the T-Shirt
  * Send Your Ideas
  * Submissions

##  [makelovenotporn.tv](https://makelovenotporn.tv/) is now in beta! 

We value and respect your personal information. We take your concerns about privacy quite seriously, and seek to take reasonable efforts to protect it. When we collect information, such as your name and email address, we use it to provide you with a response to your inquiry or with information targeted to your needs. 

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Use posted on this Website, set forth the rules and policies governing your use of this Website. All capitalized terms shall have the same meaning as set forth in the Terms of Use. By using the Website, you agree to accept these policies. We may change this policy from time to time without notice. Therefore we recommend you check back periodically to ensure you are comfortable with our most recent policy. Immediately after we post any changes to this policy, those changes are deemed effective, whether or not you have reviewed them. By using the Website after we post any changes to this policy, you agree to accept those changes. If at any time you choose not to accept the Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy, you may not use the Website. 

What information do we collect?

When you submit Submissions or request information from us, we collect your name and email address.

We may also collect non-personal or clickstream information from you when you access our Website. This can include, among other things, the type of browser you are using, the address of the website from which your visit originated, the operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, the pages you visit on the Website, and the duration of your visit.

Is your information safe with us?

Except as noted below, we donÃ­t share or sell your personal information. As necessary, we may share non-personal information with our trusted third party service providers, such as the corporations that manage or host our Website, to perform services on our behalf. They typically use non-personal, anonymous informationÃ³like clickstream information regarding visit durationÃ³that isnÃ­t identifiable with a particular visitor to further improve the Website.

The only time when we may share your personal information with a third party is in response to a legal process and/or where we (or an enforcement agency) believe your actions may violate applicable laws, or our user agreement, or where we believe your actions threaten the rights, property or safety of our company, its users (or the general public).

We take steps consistent with commercially reasonable industry standards to assure that any personal information collected from you is secured from loss, misuse or unauthorized access while under our control. Please note that despite our efforts to protect information provided to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be lost, disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.

Is Operator responsible for external links or referrals?

The Website may link to other third party websites. We are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy policies of third party websites. No judgment, endorsement, or warranty is made with respect to other websites, their security, or the content they contain, and we take no responsibility for them. Any use you make of the information provided on the Website, or any website or service linked to by the Website, is at your own risk.

Do we collect personal information from children?

The Website is not directed at anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you are not authorized to use the Website. 

This policy was last modified February 2009; any changes will be posted and noted here. If you have any questions, please contact us at info@makelovenotporn.com
